Emily Joy Plater

Date of Birth: 10/11/85 3241 NE 73rd Ave Cell Phone: 503-583-1682 Portland E-mail: plateremily@hotmail.com Oregon, 97213

Personal Profile

I have recently arrived in Portland from Nottingham, England, and feel I have much to offer with my extensive experience in customer service and hospitality roles.

From a young age I have been given responsibilities that have required me to relate to a wide range of people, this is where my strengths lie.

I am a subtle but strong individual who is a calm, positive presence, and I feel I bring a valuable dynamic to a work environment.

Relevant Skills

- o Experience in the particulars of service work- etiquette, professionalism, flexibility
- o Essential organization skills- including good time management and ability to multitask
- o Front of house experience- ability to put the customer at ease and assist as needed
- o Consistent customer care- including an understanding of customer/server rapport
- o Ability to adhere to company systems and policy- able to following instruction well

Job History

- o Server Portland Seafood Company, Portland USA: Nov 2011- Present
- o Farm Hand (Voluntary Position) Riverside Farm, McMinnville, USA: Aug 2011- Sept 2011
- o Hotel Receptionist (Maternity Cover) The Beeches Hotel, UK: Feb 2011- Aug 2011
- o Various Temporary Job Agency Positions Office Angels, UK: Aug 2010- Feb 2011
- o Receptionist (Temporary Position) Queens Medical Centre, UK: March 2010- July 2010
- o Office Receptionist Atkins Ltd, Nottingham, UK: Feb 2008- March 2010
- Receptionist/ Joint Project Manager Trees for Life, Kansas, USA: July 2007- Dec 2007
- o Wedding Waitress (Summer Job) Newagen Seaside Inn, Maine, USA: June 2006- Aug 2006
- Waitress Ashmores Restaurant, Radcliffe on Trent, UK: October 2000- July 2004

Education

O BA (Hons) American Studies - 2:2

(Lancaster University: 2004-2005, 2006-2007) (The University of Maine, USA: 2005-2006 -Study abroad year)

- A Level's 2 B's- English Literature, A Level, Media Studies, A Level 2 C's- Psychology, A Level, Human Biology, AS Level (High Pavement Sixth Form College, Nottingham: 2002-2004)
- GSCE's 8 A's- English Literature, Speaking and Language, Media Studies,
 Science (Double award), Geography, Drama, Food Technology
 1 B- Mathematics, 1 C- German, (Dayncourt School, Nottingham: 2000-2002)